Looks like a burial .
In the road ?
Driver , what is it ?
It 's a funeral , Mademoiselle .
They are afraid of the men who steal dead bodies .
So they dig the grave in the middle of the road
where people pass all the time .
Well , that 's a cheerful introduction for you to our West Indies .
Do you know where is the house of monsieur Beaumont ?
Zombies ! Aller vite ! Allez !
It felt like hands touching me !
Why did you drive like that , you fool ? We might have been killed !
Worse than that , Monsieur . We might have been caught .
Caught ? By whom ? Those men you spoke to ?
They are not men Monsieur , they are dead bodies .
Dead ?
Yes , Monsieur . Zombies .
The living dead .
Corpses taken from their graves who are made to work in sugar mills
and fields at nights .
Look ! Here they come !
Look ! Look !
Excuse me please , have you got a match ?
Did I frighten you ? Ha , I 'm sorry . I 'm oddly enough I suppose .
No , it wasn 't you .
Something happened back on the road there .
We stopped to speak to some men .
Our driver told us that they weren 't men at all . He said they were corpses .
Corpses ?
Surely you don 't believe it , do you ?
No . But I don 't know , Haiti is full of nonsense and superstition .
They 're always mixed up with a lot of mysteries that will turn your hair grey .
I 've been a missionary here for , oh , thirty years ,
and at times I don 't know what to think .
Come , let 's go in the house .
Oh , yes , come , dear .
Is Mr. Beaumont in ?
You are expected , Dr. Bruner .
Yes ... I 've been sent for to marry someone .
Maybe you ...
How long is it that you 've known Mr. Beaumont ?
Oh , only a few days .
Madeline introduced him on the docks in Port-au-Prince .
Ah , and you ?
I met him on the ship coming from New York .
He was very kind during the voyage .
Madeline and I planned to be married the moment she arrived ,
but Mr. Beaumont persuaded us to come here .
And he promised to take me out of the bank at Port-au-Prince
and send me to New York as his agent .
Strange .
Very strange .
You ...
I 'll tell Mr. Beaumont you are here .
It 's all right , isn 't it , doctor ?
Oh , I guess so .
You see I , I 've only met Mr. Beaumont once or twice .
But he never struck me like the man who would take the trouble
to play fairy godfather to a young couple like you ...
Unless ...
Unless what , sir ?
I suppose you 'll think I 'm a meddling old fool , but ...
You know , I 'd feel a good deal better if you 'd clear out of this place
after you 're married ,
and have nothing more to do with Mr. Beaumont .
The young people have arrived sir , and Dr. Bruner .
They are waiting in the reception hall .
Show them to their rooms , and tell them I 'm out .
No wait .
Perhaps I 'd better see them .
It might look odd if I didn 't .
Very odd , sir .
Especially as Dr. Bruner is a trifle skeptical as to your ... motives , sir .
Nevermind my motives .
Has that other person sent word yet ?
No , sir . Not yet .
He 's twenty-four hours late .
I wish you 'd keep away from that man , sir .
He 'll make trouble for you .
You needn 't worry about that .
I 'm not affraid of him .
I 'm not easily frightened , sir . You should know that .
But what you are planning is dangerous .
Don 't you suppose I know that , Silver ?
You don 't seem to realize what this girl means to me .
Why , I 'd sacrifice anything I have in the world for her .
Nothing matters if I can 't have her .
I think , ah , I think you 'll like Haiti . Most people that ...
Madeline ! I 'm delighted to see you ! Neil , you 're more than welcome .
Thank you , sir .
Doctor , it is very kind of you to come .
I know what a busy man you are .
No , ah , not at all . There is a native family live out here
that I 've been trying to see for a long time .
After this young couple are safely married , I 'll leave .
But surely you will stay for dinner after the ceremony ?
No , no , no . No , I must run along .
That 's a great pity . We have something very special prepared for this occasion .
It was very good of you , Madeline , to humour the whim of a lonely man .
There was so little time to prepare ,
I couldn 't do half the things I wanted for you .
You 've done more than enough already Mr. Beaumont ,
for a comparative ... giving Neil a position in The States .
Neil ?
Yes . Yes indeed .
Oh , yes of course ! I 'm sure Neil will make a very good agent .
But you must be tired after your drive .
You get some rest . Silver !
Silver will show you to your rooms .
This way please .
Delighted to see you again , monsieur Beaumont !
Please .
I 'm sorry to have kept you waiting , monsieur .
I 've been on a journey
seeking men for my mills .
Men ?
They work faithfully ... They are not worried about long hours .
You ... can make good use of men like mine on your plantations .
No .
That 's not what I want .
Then perhaps we should talk about the young lady
who came to your house this evening ?
You 've seen her ? When ?
The road , tonight .
There was a young man with her .
They are to be married , tonight .
You waited too long to do anything .
What do you want me to do ?
If she were to disappear , for a month ...
What do you hope to gain by her disappearance ?
Everything ...
Everything ?
Do you think she will forget her lover in a month ?
Just give me a month . One little month .
Not in a month . Not even a year , monsieur .
I looked into her eyes . She is deep in love . But not with you .
They are to be married within an hour !
There must be a way !
There is way .
The cost ...
The cost is heavy !
You give me what I want , and you may ask anything .
No ! Not that !
Only a pin point , monsieur Beaumont ,
in a glass of wine or perhaps a flower .
Take it . The time is very brief .
You must do your share if I am to help you .
Keep it , monsieur .
Keep it . You may change your mind .
Send me word when you use it .
- I 'll find another way . - There is no other way .
They are driving away evil spirits !
Close it , close it !
Mademoiselle !
I love you , Madeline , more than anything else in this whole world , dear .
Heaven or hell lies in this little moment for me .
You could raise me up to paradise or you could blast my world into nothingness .
I can make you the envy of every woman .
I 'd give my life to make you happy !
Oh , listen to me dear before it 's too late !
Don 't , please .
Don 't go into that room .
We can be in Port-au-Prince in half an hour .
There 's a boat sailing at midnight .
You 've been so wonderful .
Don 't spoil everything now .
One last gift before I lose you forever !
We are gathered together here in the sight of God ,
and in the face of this company ,
to join together this man , this woman
in holy matrimony .
This is the night of nights !
A toast to the bride ! To beauty 's queen !
Gladly , My Lord !
Leave but a kiss within the glass .
Fair gypsy , read my fortune .
What do you see in the glass ?
I see happiness ...
I see love , far more than you can bear .
Is that all ?
No .
I see ...
What is it ?
I see death .
Madelin !
Madeline , what 's wrong ?
Madeline my dear , please .
Oh , no ...
Madeline ? Madeline ?
Can 't we do something ?
Please , please .
Madeline !
Not my wife . My wife !
Praise of our lord and saviour and the love of god
and the fellowship of his angels .
Be with us ever more . Amen .
Neil , Neil ...
Neil ...
Neil ... Neil ...
Look !
Zombies !
Yes . They are my servants .
Did you think we could do it alone ?
In their lifetime they were my enemies .
Ledot , the witch doctor . Once my master .
Secrets I tortured out of him .
Von Gelder , the swine . Swollen with riches .
He fought against my spells until the last . In him I have a struggling type .
His Excellence , Richard . Once minister of the interior .
Scarpia , Brigand Chief . Marcquis , Captain of Gendarmerie ... .
And this , this is Chauvin , the high executioner ,
who almost executed me !
I took them
just as we will take this one .
But what if they regain their souls ?
They would tear me to pieces .
But that , my friend , shall never be .
Madeline !
There 's two explanations that strike me ,
either the body was stolen by the members of a death cult
that use human bones in their ceremonies , or else ...
Or else what ?
She 's not dead .
Not dead ?
Are you mad ?
I saw her die , the doctor signed the certificate .
I saw them bury her .
Now , wait a minute , wait a minute , I 'm not mad .
But I 've lived in these islands for a good many years ,
and I 've seen things with my eyes that made me think I was crazy .
There are superstitions in Haiti that the natives brought here from Africa .
Some of them can be traced back as far as ancient Egypt ,
and beyond that yet , in the countries that was old when Egypt was young .
Yes , but what has that to do with Madeline ?
I kissed her as she lay there in the coffin .
And her lips were cold .
Let me explain . Now , just a minute , I 'll explain .
Wherever there is a superstition , you will find there is also a practice .
Now , do you remember what your driver told you
the night that he took you to Beaumont 's house ?
Oh , about those horrible creatures we saw ?
He said they were corpses ! Taken from their graves .
Yes - that 's the superstition ! Now for the practice .
The ghouls that steal the dead corpses from their graves ,
are supposed to put them there in the first place .
Do you mean that Madeline was murdered
so that somebody could steal her dead body ?
Aagh ! Nonsense !
No , no . Not her ...
Her body , yes . But not her dead body . That 's what I meant .
Well , surely you don 't think she 's alive , in the hands of natives ?
Oh no , better dead than that !
Excuse me please , have you got a match ?
Thank you .
You don 't believe that , do you ?
Say , there 's been lots of people that 's been pronounced dead
that came alive again and lived for years .
Now , if nature can play pranks like that ,
why isn 't it possible to play pranks with nature ?
Oh , I don 't know .
Your driver believed he saw dead men , walking .
He didn 't . What he saw was men alive
and everything but this and this .
Oh , the whole thing has me confused !
I just can 't understand it .
Um , I don 't blame you ... I don 't blame you .
I 've been trying for years to get to the bottom of these things .
To separate what you call fact from fiction .
The law !
The law of Haiti acknowledges the possibility of being buried alive .
Here it is in the penal code . I 'll read it for you .
It 's in French , do you speak French ?
No .
Excuse me please , have you got a match ?
Right here , here 's one .
Oh , thank you . I didn 't see it there .
I 'll translate it for you . If you could spare me .
Article ...
Article 2.49 .
The use ... The use of drugs or other practices
which produce lethargic coma , or lifeless sleep ,
shall be considered attempted murder .
Attempted !
Yes I see .
If the person has been buried alive ,
the act should be considered murder
no matter what result follows .
Beaumont !
Say , you said you couldn 't understand why he was so interested in us .
Do you think he did this ?
No . No , I think his natives would .
Natives would be right .
Of course if you want to , we could go to Beaumont 's house first .
If I could get my hands on the devil that 's responsible for this ,
I 'll make him such an example that every witch doctor in Haiti
would be shaking in his sandals .
But we can 't do this alone .
Can 't the authorities help ?
The authorities , Neil , my boy , you don 't know these islands .
The native authorities are afraid to meddle .
I am not . I 've got friends among the natives .
They 'll tell me things that no gendarme could ever get out of them .
Because I am a preacher .
They think I am a magician .
Before we get through with this thing , we may uncover sins
that even the devil would be ashamed of .
Oh , these witch doctors ...
Madeline ...
Foolish things , they can 't bring back the light to those eyes .
I was mad to do this , but if you had smiled on me ,
I 'd have done anything for you , given you anything .
I thought that beauty alone would satisfy , but the soul is gone ...
I can 't bear those empty staring eyes .
Oh , forgive me , Madeline . Forgive me !
I can 't bear it any longer , I must take you back .
Back to the grave , Monsieur ?
No , you must put the life back into her eyes and bring laughter to her lips .
She must be gay and happy again !
You paint a charming picture , Monsieur .
One that I should like to see myself !
You must bring her back .
Aren 't you a trifle afraid , Monsieur ?
How do suppose those eyes will regard you
when the brain is able to understand ?
Better to see hatred in them than that dreadful emptiness .
Perhaps you 're right .
It would be a pity to destroy such a lovely flower .
Let 's drink to the future of this flower .
A glass of wine !
Silver , bring wine ! We have a toast to drink .
To the future , Monsieur !
Only a pin point , Monsieur .
In a flower ...
or perhaps in a glass of wine ?
You devil ! What are you trying to do to me ?
I have other plans for Mademoiselle .
And I am afraid you might not agree .
I have taken a fancy to you , Monsieur !
Silver ! Silver !
Don 't , don 't !
To the future , Monsieur !
The vulture , you ...
No . Not that . Not that !
We ought to be picking up an old witch doctor around here pretty soon .
His name is Pierre , I 've known him for years . Bright old fellow .
I don 't know just where we 'll find him .
Come , son . There are evil spirits in the road .
I will give you an awonga . And here , this one for the ox .
Young man is sick with distress .
Well hey , wait a minute , we can 't afford to have you sick .
Neil , why don 't you go over there , we 've got a hard day before us tomorrow .
Now , now then Pierre , come on . He 's gone . We can talk .
It is a dangerous thing you ask me to do .
Well now listen here you know , we 're old friends , you and me ,
and I want to go on .
Turn back before it is too late !
Oh , no . I 've come too far to turn back now .
I 'm too old to go all this way with you .
Well listen , can 't you get somebody to go with us ?
My people all afraid of the mountain .
Why ?
Because it is called the land of the living dead .
Well , have , have you ever been there ?
I am the only man that has ever come back from there alive .
There is an evil spirit man that is called Murder .
Come , I will tell you all about what he did .
Vulture .
Just as old Pierre said .
A cloud of vultures always hovers over the house of the living dead .
Madeline ...
Is she there ?
Oh , I must go and see her .
Neil , my boy , please , please lie down and rest . Please .
You 'll feel stronger in the morning .
You rest .
Let me go up and see what I can do .
Why is she so restless tonight ?
Perhaps she remembers something ?
They never remember anything when they are like that .
No ?
Because she 's cut off .
Madeline !
No , no , I can 't ,
I can 't !
You must , it 's your turn .
Let 's run away !
He might hear you !
No way . I can 't stand it . I am going to run away !
He will find you and make you like her .
Can you still hear me ?
It is unfortunate you are no longer able to speak .
I should be interested to hear you describe your symptoms ...
You see , you are the first man to know what is happening .
None of the others did .
You refused to shake hands once .
I remember .
Well , well .
We understand each other better now .
Madeline !
Madeline ! I found you !
You 're alive . Alive !
What 's the matter ? It 's I , Neil .
Oh my darling , what have they done to you ?
Who are you ?
And what are they ?
For you , my friend , they are the angels of death .
Come ! Zombies ! Duck !
Look !
Madeline , don 't you know me , dear ?
It 's Neil .
I could swear , for a moment she recognized you .
Come on , don 't let him get away !
Madeline , my darling !
Neil , I ... I dreamed ?
Excuse me please , have you got a match ?
Re-synchronised by job0 @ whatkeepsmebusy @ today 09 / 02 / 2017